♪Come closer♪
اقترب ♪
♪Be more intimate♪
♪ كن أكثر حميمية
♪Tell me if I am tempted♪
♪ قل لي إن كنت أغوى
♪The moment you and I looked at each other♪
♪ في اللحظة التي نظرت فيها أنا وأنت إلى بعضنا البعض
♪We were both tempted♪
كلانا أغوى
♪Remember how shy you were♪
♪ تذكر كم كنت خجولًا ♪
♪That day♪
♪ ذلك اليوم ♪
♪Sweet memories♪
♪ ذكريات حلوة ♪
♪Please be more♪
♪ من فضلك كن اكثر
♪How lucky I am to have you♪
♪ كم أنا محظوظ لوجودك ♪
♪So sweet♪
♪ حلوة جدا ♪
=My Naughty Assistant=
= مساعدي المشاغب =
=Episode 3=
= الحلقة 3 =
Duoduo.
ديودو.
Who's it?
من هو؟
It's me.
هذا أنا.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
I brought you breakfast.
أحضرت لك الإفطار.
Where were you last night?
أين كنت الليلة الماضية؟
(Liang Jiawei, 27, 180cm tall, playboy)
(ليانغ جياوي ، 27 ، طوله 180 سم ، مستهتر)
Duoduo.
ديودو.
Stop being like that.
توقف عن أن تكون هكذا.
I'm being like what?
أكون مثل ماذا؟
Duo, why are you so angry?
Duo ، لماذا أنت غاضب جدًا؟
Is it because I didn't send you home after the work was done last night?
هل هذا لأنني لم أعيدك إلى المنزل بعد انتهاء العمل الليلة الماضية؟
Don't touch me. I will call the police.
لا تلمسني.  أنا سوف استدعاء الشرطة.
Are you mad at me?
هل أنت غاضب مني؟
Get out.
اخرج.
I'll call the police.
سأتصل بالشرطة.
Duo.
Duo.
Get out.
اخرج.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
What exactly have I done wrong?
ما الخطأ الذي فعلته بالضبط؟
Get out. Go to your other girlfriend.
اخرج.  اذهب إلى صديقتك الأخرى.
You jerks.
أيها الحمقى.
Sorry, could you forgive me?
آسف ، هل يمكنك أن تسامحني؟
You know.
أنت تعرف.
We were so happy together.
كنا سعداء جدا معا.
Give me one more chance, please.
أعطني فرصة أخرى من فضلك.
It was just a moment.
كانت مجرد لحظة.
Forgive me, please.
سامحني أرجوك.
(Have you no shame?)
(ألا تشعر بالخجل؟)
This photo.
هذه الصورة.
The photo I took of you.
الصورة التي التقطتها لك.
This is what we bought when traveling together.
هذا ما اشتريناه عند السفر معًا.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
I was wrong, really.
كنت مخطئا حقا.
We're done.
لقد انتهينا.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
Look at the photos we took on our last anniversary.
انظر إلى الصور التي التقطناها في ذكرى زواجنا الأخيرة.
Look at this
انظر إلى هذا
and this.
وهذا.
This was taken on our anniversary.
تم التقاط هذا في ذكرى زواجنا.
Stop doing that, or I will...
توقف عن فعل ذلك ، أو سأفعل ...
Duo.
Duo.
I was wrong.
كنت مخطئا.
I was really wrong.
كنت مخطئا حقا.
Just give me one more chance.
فقط أعطني فرصة أخرى.
Okay?
تمام؟
I'll treat you better in the future.
سوف أعاملك بشكل أفضل في المستقبل.
We've been together for four years.
نحن معا لمدة أربع سنوات.
I am petty
أنا تافه
and bear no cheating.
ولا تتحمل الغش.
Give me one more chance, please.
أعطني فرصة أخرى من فضلك.
I was really wrong.
كنت مخطئا حقا.
Forgive me.
اغفر لي.
I'll only treat you well.
سوف أعاملك بشكل جيد فقط.
I'll only love you.
سأحبك فقط.
I swear.
أقسم.
I swear to God.
اقسم بالله.
Duoduo.
ديودو.
Let's start over, shall we?
لنبدأ من جديد ، أليس كذلك؟
Not answering the phone.
عدم الرد على الهاتف.
Then why do you even have it?
ثم لماذا لديك حتى؟
(Why is he here too?)
(لماذا هو هنا أيضًا؟)
Mm,
مم،
my boyfriend is here.
صديقي هنا.
I'm not available.
أنا غير موجود.
(Boyfriend?)
(حبيب؟)
♪How many times in my life♪
♪ كم مرة في حياتي ♪
♪I am destined♪
أنا مقدر ♪
♪To meet you and fall in love with you♪
♪ لمقابلتك والوقوع في حبك
♪In my finest age♪
♪ في خيرة عمري ♪
♪It's a pity♪
♪ إنه لأمر مؤسف
♪That we are not together in this life♪
بأننا لسنا معًا في هذه الحياة
♪But still, thank you♪
♪ لكن مع ذلك ، شكرًا لك ♪
♪For letting me♪
♪ لسماحك لي ♪
♪Walk into your world♪
♪ امش في عالمك ♪